Guide to the New York State Teachers Association Records 1915-1979
New York State Teachers Association Records
- Series IV: Assistant Executive Secretary's Files
  - Sub-Series A: Kullman Subject Files
    - Sub-Series a: Commission on Professional Practices, Rights and Responsibilities. (CPP R), 1961-1970
      - Wyandanch, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 26)
      - Wyandanch-As Above. 1967 (Box 96, Folder 27)
      - Wyandanch-Report, final form. 1967 (Box 96, Folder 28)
      - Wyandanch-New clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 29)
      - Wyandanch-Second Place Exhibits, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 30)
        Contains a 1967 teachers handbook, the proposed budget for 1967-68, and the policies and regulations of the Bd. Of Ed. 1967-68
      - Wyandanch, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 31)
        As above. 1967-68
      - Wyandanch, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 32)
      - Wyandanch-Second Study Committee Visit, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 33)
        Contains background information re the CPP R revisit. Also contains an appeal re the dissolution of the Wyandanch school district. 1967-68
      - Wyandanch-Follow-Up, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 34)
      - Wyandanch-Esther Berges, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 35)
        Re disability and death benefits. 1970
      - Meeting Minutes Sept. 28, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, Dec. 14, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, General. 1957 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Minutes, Feb. 8, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Minutes, Ap. 19, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Annual Report., 1958-1966 (Box 97, Folder 6)
        1958-66
      - Correspondence, General. 1958 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, General. 1959 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Interpretation of the Code of Ethics. 1959 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Bylaw Amendment Proposals, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 10)
        Termination of Membership, change of Name E.P.C. 1962
      - Grievance Procedure. 1962-66, 1962-1966 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Minutes, March 1-2, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Oct. 24-6, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 13)
        Agenda book #1
      - Meeting Oct. 24-6, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 14)
        Agenda book #2
      - Meeting Oct. 24-6, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 15)
        Correspondence
      - Meeting Oct. 24-6, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 16)
        Materials
      - Meeting Oct. 24-6, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 17)
        Minutes
      - Correspondence 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 20)
      - Professional Guidebook. 1963 (Box 97, Folder 21)
      - Meetings, General, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 22)
        Agendas. 1964
      - Meetings Feb. 13-14, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 23)
      - Meetings, Feb. 13-14, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 24)
      - Meeting Minutes, Feb. 27-29, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 25)
      - Meeting Minutes, Feb. 27-29, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 26)
      - Meeting, Agenda book #1, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 27)
        Feb. 27-March 1, 1964
      - Meeting, Agenda Book #2, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 28)
      - Meeting, Materials, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 29)
      - Meeting, Materials, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 30)
      - Meeting, Utah Investigation., 1964 (Box 97, Folder 31)
        Feb 27- March 1, 1964
      - Meeting May 22-23, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 32)
      - Meeting, May 22-23, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 33)
      - Meeting, June 20-23, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 34)
        Agenda book. 1964
      - Meeting, June 20-23, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 35)
      - Meeting Correspondence and reports., 1964 (Box 97, Folder 36)
        June 20-23, 1964
      - Meeting Correspondence and Reports, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Materials, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 3)
        Oct. 1-2, 1964
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Meeting Materials, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 5)
        Oct. 1-3, 1964
      - Meeting Minutes, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Meeting Correspondence, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 7)
        Oct. 24-26, 1964
      - Meeting Minutes, General, 1964-1967 (Box 98, Folder 8)
        1964-67
      - Workshop Program book (Box 98, Folder 9)
        June 24-26
      - Meetings of Subcommittee on Human Rights of Education, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Meetings of Subcommittee on Human Rights of Education. 1965 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Meetings of Subcommittee on Human Rights of Education. 1965, 1965-1965 (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - Meetings of Subcommittee on Human Rights of Education. 1965 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Meeting Materials, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 14)
        Feb. 4-6, 1965
      - Meeting Materials, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 15)
      - Meeting Materials, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 16)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 17)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 18)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 19)
      - Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 20)
        Fe. 4-6, 1965
      - Meeting, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 21)
        Feb. 19-20, 1965
      - Meeting, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 22)
      - Meeting, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 23)
        Ap. 30-May 1, 1965
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 24)
        June 23-25, 1965
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 25)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 26)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Materials, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 2)
        June 23-July 2, 1965
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 3)
        Oct. 7-9, 1965
      - Meeting Agenda book, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Meeting Agenda Book (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Making Minutes, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence and Materials, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Workshop, General Correspondence and Materials, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Meeting. Jan. 21-22, 1966, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 10)
        Feb. 3-5, 1966
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Agenda Book, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 13)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 14)
      - Meeting Miscellaneous Materials, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 15)
        Feb.-March, 1966
      - Meeting, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 16)
        Ap. 1-2, 1966
      - Meeting, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 17)
        May 20-21, 1966
      - Attendance,Teacher Duties, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 18)
      - Bill of Rights for Teachers (Box 99, Folder 19)
        1966-67
      - Bill of Rights Survey (Box 99, Folder 20)
      - Bill of Rights Survey (Box 99, Folder 21)
      - Bill of Rights Survey (Box 99, Folder 22)
      - Bill of Rights Survey (Box 99, Folder 23)
      - Joint TEPS-PPR R Project (Box 99, Folder 24)
        See also "TEPS" in KSF-general series.1967-68
      - Meeting. Feb. 24-25, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 25)
      - Meeting. Feb. 24-25, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 26)
      - Meeting. Feb. 24-25, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 27)
      - Meeting. (Box 100, Folder 1)
        May 12-13, 1967
      - Meeting. (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Meeting. Aug. 22, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - General Materials. 1967 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Bill of rights (Box 100, Folder 5)
        Responses of CPP R. 1967
      - Reports and Correspondence of the Sub-Committee on Human Rights (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Reports and Correspondence of the Sub-Committee on Human Rights (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Materials of the Subcommittee on Human Rights (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Materials of the Subcommittee on Human Rights (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence of the Subcommittee on Human Rights (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence of the Subcommittee on Human Rights (Box 100, Folder 11)
        Jan. 26-27, 1968
      - Joint CPP R (Box 100, Folder 12)
        NYS School boards Ethics Committee Meeting. Ap. 5, 1968
      - Meeting. Aug. 20, 22, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - Meeting. Nov. 8-9, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - California Statement of Ethics (Box 100, Folder 15)
        Administrator Ethics in Personal Matters. 1968
      - Annual Report. 1968 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - Clinic. Aug. 24, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - September Mailings: Webutuck, Peru, etc. 1968 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - September Proposed Revision of Joint Code of Ethics. 1968 (Box 100, Folder 19)
      - Oct. 11 Mailings: Oceanside Dispute, Zone Responsibilities, Certification, etc. 1968 (Box 100, Folder 20)
      - Peru Inquiry and Teacher Rights Fund and Board Minutes (Box 100, Folder 21)
        Oct. 18, 1968
      - Nov. 20 Maining Re: (Box 100, Folder 22)
        Nominations to the professional practices panel, Jamestown impasse, etc. 1968
      - December Mailings Re (Box 100, Folder 23)
        Academia freedom. 1968
      - Minutes of Meetings and Agendas (Box 100, Folder 24)
      - Meeting, March 21-22 (Box 100, Folder 25)
      - Meeting (Box 100, Folder 26)
        April 25-26, 1969
      - Meetings (Box 100, Folder 27)
        Sept. 26-27, 1969
      - Meeting (Box 100, Folder 28)
        May 23-24, 1969
      - Meeting (Box 100, Folder 29)
      - Meeting (Box 100, Folder 30)
      - Meeting. (Box 100, Folder 31)
        Nov. 8-9, 1969
      - Meeting (Box 100, Folder 32)
        Dec. 14-15, 1969
      - Annual Report (Box 100, Folder 33)
      - Case Reports (Box 100, Folder 34)
        Beckman, Bethpage, Dover Plains, Falconer, Great Neck, Herrick, Port Washington, Peru. 1969
      - Meeting re Falconer-Herricks etc. (Box 100, Folder 35)
        March 13, 1969
      - Meeting re Garden City etc. (Box 100, Folder 36)
        March 28, 1969
      - Meeting re Great Neck Local Issues etc. (Box 100, Folder 37)
        April 4, 1969
      - April 8th Mailing. 1969 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - April 11th Mailing. 1969 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Reports and Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 3)
        ..and academic freedom policy. 1969
      - Meetings (Box 101, Folder 4)
        Jan. Feb., April, 1970
      - Meetings (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Meeting. Feb. 27-28, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Meeting. Feb. 27-28, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Meeting Correspondence and Materials (Box 101, Folder 8)
        March 20-21, 1970
      - Meeting Correspondence and Materials (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Meeting Minutes, Materials and Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 10)
        May 22-23, 1970
      - Meeting Minutes, Materials and Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Annual Report. 1970 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Sub-Series b. General Subject files
      this series contains Kullman's general subject files concerning his duties as Assistant Executive Secretary. They are arranged alphabetically by key word. Boxes 318-321 contain his files on the Council on Administrative Leadership (CA:) arranged alphabetically within that title. This series has a good deal of material on the Ethical Practices Committee and TEPS council which should be used in conjunction with Series IV-A-s
      - Sub-Series 1: Council and Administrative Leadership (CAL)
        - "A Man's Reach" (Box 101, Folder 13)
          A motion picture. Correspondence and publicity, 1961-65
        - Administering Tomorrow's Schools (Box 101, Folder 14)
          by Robert. H. Howsman- delivered at seminar for School Administrators and correspondence. 1966
        - Administration and Organization of the high School (Box 101, Folder 15)
          A paper by R.P. Schmidle-correspondence, etc., 1968
        - "The Relationship of Selected Administrative Procedures to School Bond Interest Rates" (Box 101, Folder 16)
          by. R. Ten Haken, 1968
        - Study: How to Recognize, Recruit and Select Potential Leaders in Education Administration (Box 101, Folder 17)
          1959
        - Study of Administrators Salary (Box 101, Folder 18)
          1957-60
        - Advisory Committee on Staffing and Organizing the Elementary School (Box 101, Folder 19)
          Report and correspondence, 1958-60
        - Belief Systems and Chief School Administrators Attitude toward Educational Innovation (Box 101, Folder 20)
          by Burton Ramer Robert Heller, 1967
        - Bill for Certification of Superintendents (Box 101, Folder 21)
          Mostly correspondence, 1958-61
        - Collective Teacher Power and Action (Box 101, Folder 22)
          paper by Frank Lutz, 1968
        - Ethics Committee, 1958-59 (Box 101, Folder 23)
        - House of Delegates (Box 101, Folder 24)
        - House of Representatives (Box 101, Folder 25)
          1962-1963
        - House of Representatives (Box 101, Folder 26)
          1962-63
        - House of Representatives (Box 101, Folder 27)
        - House of Representatives (Box 101, Folder 28)
        - 3rd Annual House of Representatives (Box 101, Folder 29)
          Contains platform, position statements, correspondence, etc., 1964
        - 3rd Annual House of Representatives (Box 101, Folder 30)
        - House of Representatives (Box 102, Folder 1)
          1967 materials
        - Drafts of Leaflets (Box 102, Folder 2)
          1960-66
        - Drafts of Leaflets (Box 102, Folder 3)
        - Drafts of Leaflets (Box 102, Folder 4)
        - Drafts of Leaflets (Box 102, Folder 5)
        - Minutes of Meetings (Box 102, Folder 6)
          1965-68
        - NYS Assoc. of Directors of Health, Physical Education Recreation (Box 102, Folder 7)
          Correspondence papers, 1957-58
        - Policy Statements on Employment Practices (Box 102, Folder 8)
          etc. 1959-60
        - Problem Census Study (Box 102, Folder 9)
          re: problems of public schools, 1957
        - Problem Census (Box 102, Folder 10)
          An evaluation of the public schools, correspondence, reports, etc. 1959
        - Problem Census Follow-Up (Box 102, Folder 11)
          1958
        - Task of Public Schools (Box 102, Folder 12)
          Correspondence reports, 1961
        - Salary Study, 1957-58 (Box 102, Folder 13)
        - Salary Study, 1959-60 (Box 102, Folder 14)
        - Salary Study (NY) Principals, 1957-58 (Box 102, Folder 15)
        - Salary Survey, 1957-58 (Box 102, Folder 16)
        - Salary Survey, 1957-58 (Box 102, Folder 17)
      - Sub-Series 2: Other Subject Files
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates (Box 102, Folder 18)
          Mostly minutes and correspondence, 1970
        - Alternative Directors (Box 102, Folder 19)
          bylaw amendments concerning and other areas, correspondence, 1971
        - Bay Shore Election Protest (Box 102, Folder 20)
          Correspondence, subcommittee reports, Bay shore position, papers, etc., re election of delegates to House, 1965
        - Bay Shore Election Protest (Box 102, Folder 21)
        - Mr. Bestor Refuted (Box 102, Folder 22)
          A paper by Virgil Rogers about America's Public Schools, 1956
        - Board of Directors Meetings (Box 102, Folder 23)
        - Board of Directors Meetings (Box 102, Folder 24)
        - Board of Directors Meetings (Box 102, Folder 25)
        - Board of Directors Unification Task Force (Box 103, Folder 1)
          1972
        - The Conference of Large city Boards of Education of NYS (Box 103, Folder 2)
        - Building Needs Committee, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 3)
        - Arvid J. Burke Fellowship (Box 103, Folder 4)
          Correspondence and description, 1967-71
        - Bylaw Proposals-NYSTA, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 5)
        - Certification of Trade Technical Supervisors (Box 103, Folder 6)
          a CAL project, 1958
        - Classroom Teacher's Association-1970 (Box 103, Folder 7)
        - Classroom Teachers Council and Professional Advancement (Box 103, Folder 8)
          Correspondence and reports 1969-70
        - Committee Worksheets (Box 103, Folder 9)
          re: appointments to committees, 1967-68
        - Committees-Nominations to (Box 103, Folder 10)
        - Committees-Nominations to (Box 103, Folder 11)
        - Community Colleges (Box 103, Folder 12)
          Some ACCF material, 1970
        - Constitutional Convention Committee, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 13)
        - Constitutional Convention Committee, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence-General (Box 103, Folder 15)
          1960-62
        - Correspondence re Appointment to Committees (Box 103, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence re Membership (Box 103, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence to Membership (Box 103, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence to PPRR Commission Members (Box 103, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence re Teacher Draft Status (Box 103, Folder 20)
        - Councils and Committees (Box 103, Folder 21)
          General reports, etc. includes judicial nominating and legislative, etc. 1969-72
        - Councils, Commissions and Committees of NYSTA (Box 103, Folder 22)
          lists, correspondence, 1965-67
        - Councils, Commissions Committees of NYSTA (Box 103, Folder 23)
        - Credentials Committee, 1969-70 (Box 103, Folder 24)
        - Curriculum Supervision and Instruction Specialists (Box 103, Folder 25)
          Correspondence and reports for the curriculum leaderships group and others. 1962
        - Committee on Decentralization. 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1)
        - Classroom Desegregation (Box 104, Folder 2)
          "How it Will Work" by Henry Garrett, 1965-67
        - Disability Benefits Law (Box 104, Folder 3)
          memos and correspondence, 1963
        - Eastern Regional Institute for Education (Box 104, Folder 4)
          report, 1968
        - Arvie Eldred Scholarship Committee (Box 104, Folder 5)
          report of 1970 awards, 1969-70
        - Special Committee re Election District (Box 104, Folder 6)
          Procedures in relation to legislation, 1970
        - Advisory Committee for Equal Educational Opportunity (Box 104, Folder 7)
        - Teacher Action for Equal Educational Opportunity (Box 104, Folder 8)
          Reports-information leaflets, and correspondence, 1969-70
        - Ethical Practices Committee (Box 104, Folder 9)
          1950-60
        - Ethical Practices Committee (Box 104, Folder 10)
        - Ethical Practices SEE: Joint Code of Ethics (Box 104, Folder 11)
        - Ethical Practices Committee (Box 104, Folder 12)
          Correspondence, 1952
        - Ethical Practice Committee (Box 104, Folder 13)
          general corresp. And reports, 1955-58
        - Ethical Practices and Professional Ed. Comm. (Box 104, Folder 14)
          Sept. 30-October 1, 1958
        - Ethical Practices-General (Box 104, Folder 15)
          1958-60
        - Ethical Practices-General (Box 104, Folder 16)
        - Ethical Practices Committee (EPC) (Box 104, Folder 17)
          February 28, 1959-meeting
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 18)
          Correspondence-general-1959
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 19)
          general corres. report, 1959
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 20)
          questionnaire on local associations, 1959
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 21)
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 22)
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 23)
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 24)
          questionnaire on local assn., 1959
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 25)
          re Saratoga Springs, 1960
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 26)
          Investigation in Saratoga-also other investigations, 1960
        - EPC-Feb. 1960-Jan. 1961 (Box 104, Folder 27)
        - EPC (Box 104, Folder 28)
          warns on certain employment practices, ND
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 1)
          correspondence-cases, 1960-65
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 2)
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 3)
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 4)
          meeting, Nov. 2, 1962
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 5)
          meeting-includes handbooks draft-Jan 26-27, 1962
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 6)
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 7)
        - EPC (Box 105, Folder 8)
        - Code of Ethics for the Teaching Profession (Box 105, Folder 9)
          1959-1961
        - Code of Ethics for the Teaching Profession (Box 105, Folder 10)
        - Proposed Code of Ethics (Box 105, Folder 11)
          1961-62
        - Interpretations of the Code of Ethics (Box 105, Folder 12)
          nd
        - Joint Sub-Committee (Box 105, Folder 13)
          revision of the Joint Code of Ethics, 1968
        - Joint Sub-Committee (Box 105, Folder 14)
        - Dr. G.J. Fabiano (Box 105, Folder 15)
          Consultant to NHEA, NYSTA SPA -this is his daily log-publicity elections, etc., 1970
        - Finance Committee (Box 105, Folder 16)
          report summary of expenses, 1969-70
        - Memos to Mr. Goold (Box 105, Folder 17)
          1960-64
        - Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations (Box 105, Folder 18)
          March 31-final report, 1966
        - Committee on Headquarters, Regional Offices, Election Districts (Box 105, Folder 19)
        - Statement of Pres. Hobart to Democratic Platform Hearing (Box 105, Folder 20)
          June 16, 1972
        - Committee on House of Delegates (Box 105, Folder 21)
          Corres. And reports, 1968
        - Committee on House of Delegates-1970 (Box 105, Folder 22)
        - House of Delegates (Box 105, Folder 23)
          delegates material NEK notes, letters, etc.-reports, 1964
        - House of Delegates (HOD) (Box 105, Folder 24)
          resolutions comm., letters, etc. and general material, 1964
        - HOD-1967 (Box 105, Folder 25)
        - HOD-1967 (Box 105, Folder 26)
        - HOD-1967 (Box 105, Folder 27)
        - HOD-1968 (Box 105, Folder 28)
        - HOD-1969 (Box 105, Folder 29)
        - HOD-1969 (Box 106, Folder 1)
        - Memo on Huntington Strike to LI Local Assn. President (Box 106, Folder 2)
          memo & clippings & letters, 1968
        - Maturing Opportunities for In-Service Education of Educational Administrator (Box 106, Folder 3)
          by Kenneth Frasure-a paper & corres., 1967
        - Institutional Teachers (Box 106, Folder 4)
        - Instructional Improvement Committee (Box 106, Folder 5)
        - Insurance Program (Box 106, Folder 6)
          1968-70
        - Desirable Investigation Practices for NYSTA Ethics (Box 106, Folder 7)
          1955
        - Legal Assistance Screening Committee (Box 106, Folder 8)
          Correspondence, etc., 1964
        - Legal Assistance Screening Committee (Box 106, Folder 9)
        - Legislative Program-1968 (Box 106, Folder 10)
        - Legislative Program-1970 (Box 106, Folder 11)
        - Legislative Task Force (Box 106, Folder 12)
          correspondence, 1970
        - Local Assn. Survey (Box 106, Folder 13)
          re: Committees on PPR R, 1959
        - Long Island Teachers Committee for Action (Box 106, Folder 14)
          (LITCA)- correspondence/ meeting-1966
        - Mary Muldoon Teacher Assistance, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 15)
        - Merger Agreement with UTNY (Box 106, Folder 16)
        - NEA (Box 106, Folder 17)
          Annual meeting-June 20- July 4, 1958
        - NEA Convention (Box 106, Folder 18)
          Correspondence convention delegate materials, 1966
        - NEA (Box 106, Folder 19)
          code of ethics, 1966-68
        - NEA (Box 106, Folder 20)
          development project-correspondence, reports, 1966-67
        - NEA (Box 106, Folder 21)
          financial reports, 1969
        - NEA-Regional Conference for State Assoc. Staff Members (Box 106, Folder 22)
        - NEA Representative Assembly (Box 106, Folder 23)
          material for assembly and correspondence, 1967
        - NEA Representative Assembly (Box 106, Folder 24)
        - NEA Representative Assembly (Box 106, Folder 25)
        - Negotiations, Impasse, Work Stoppages (Box 106, Folder 26)
          memo's regarding-1968-70
        - New York City-Guidelines Committee (Box 106, Folder 27)
          correspondence reports, 1963